>> 演讲者 1: 引领整个讨论，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: So
leading this entire discussion,
我们一直在说我们想知道我们的类型
we've been saying that we
want to know our types.
我们希望使用一种编码方式，使我们的类型更加明显。
We want to use a coding style that
makes our types more obvious.
到这个地步，我一直在用我们所知的关于 JavaScript 的事情来做。
And up to this point I've been using only
what we know about JavaScript to do that.
我一直建议我们可以限制可以进来的
I've been suggesting that we can restrict
the kinds of values that can come in for
例如，类型比较。
type comparisons, for example.
我认为这是一个有效的
And I think that is a valid and
有价值的方法可提高代码的质量。
worthwhile approach that will
improve the quality of your code.
不管你喜欢还是
Regardless of whether you like or
不像 TypeScript 和 Flow 之类的输入系统的当前趋势。
dislike the current trend towards these
typing systems like TypeScript and Flow.
我要在一个更广泛的类别中说，请注意类型。
And I'm gonna say in a broader category,
type-aware linting.
正如我们刚才所说， linting 本质上是一种应用观点的工具。
As we said earlier, linting is essentially
a tool that applies an opinion about
把你的意见给你让你自己决定你知道吗
your code and gives you that opinion so
that you can decide, you know what?
我同意我不该那么做
I agree I shouldn't do that.
我的林子捕捉到各种我不想做的事
My linter catches all kinds of
things that I don't wanna do, and
我很高兴我的林特抓住了它
I'm glad my linter catches it.
我很支持 linting的想法
I'm very much pro the idea of linting.
就像我说的我只支持可以配置的
As I said,
I'm only pro linting that is configurable,
但是，因为没有一个尺寸适合所有。
however, because there is
not a one size fits all.
现在，我并不像你们中的许多人一样，在一个团队中。
Now, I'm not in the situation like many
of you are, where you're on a team.
但即便是在做出决定的情况下
But even with respect to
making that decision,
你应该还能让队伍以民主方式决定
you should still be able to have
the team decide democratically.
不是团队只能选
Rather than the team only be able to pick
世界上每一支队伍都做了些什么
what every other team in
the entire world has done.
最好还是由团队来决定为他们做什么，
It's still better that the team could
decide what works for them, and
团队的个人成员会有这么多的东西
that the individual members of the team
get to have a say-so in what that is.
我们称之为 " 风格指导" 。
We call that style guidance.
那是一个老的学期
That's an old school term.
您的团队需要样式指南，并且
Your team needs a style guide, and
大家应该在样式指南中投一票。
everybody should have
a vote in the style guide.
我不喜欢我去和一个团队合作的时候
I don't like it when I go and
work with a team, and there's some
在为每个人做出决定的团队中仁慈的仁慈的独裁者
benevolent dictator on the team that has
made all the decisions for everybody.
在休息的时候人们会来找我
And people come up to me
during the breaks and
他们就像我害怕的那样他会拒绝我的要求
they're like I'm scared to try this
cuz he's gonna reject my pull request.
这不是一种健康的文化。
That's not a healthy culture.
每个人都应该为你的团队做些什么不是我
Everybody should get a say-so in
what works for your team, not me.
你和你的队员应该说
You and
your team members should get to say.
>> 演讲者 1: 从广义上讲，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: So broadly speaking,
我有很多次这个问题，你是怎么想到 TypeScript 的 ??
I get a lot of times this question of
what do you think about TypeScript??
我想的是 " TypeScript " 和 " 流 " 的想法是相似的
Well, what I think about TypeScript and
what I think about Flow are similar,
我很高兴他们的存在尽管我不使用它们
which is I'm glad that they exist
even though I don't use them.
我不使用 TypeScript ，我不使用流，我曾告诉人们
I don't use TypeScript and I don't
use Flow, and I used to tell people
我之所以不这样做是因为他们解决了我没有的问题
the reason I don't do that is because
they solve problems that I don't have.
我现在对这个有不同的看法
I have a different
perspective on that now,
一个最近进化的观点
a perspective that has evolved recently.
不是我不用的，因为我没有
It is not the case that I don't
use them because I don't have
他们解决的同样问题，不是说它的合适方式。
the same problems that they solve,
that's not the appropriate way to say it.
我不使用那些工具或者不喜欢那些工具
I don't use those tools or
don't prefer those tools,
因为他们用一种我认为让我的代码更糟的方式来解决这些问题
because they're fixing the problems in
a way that I think makes my code worse.
正如我在我们讨论的这个单元中一再指出的，问题是存在的。
Problems exist, as I have said over and
over again in this unit of our discussion,
如果您正在编码并且不了解有关您的类型的任何信息，那么这是一个问题。
it is a problem if you are coding and
not knowing anything about your types.
这是一个问题，我们应该解决这个问题。
That is a problem and
we should solve that problem.
只是我对如何解决这个问题有不同的看法，你和我吗 ?
It's just that I have a different
opinion on how to solve it, you with me?
所以在我跟你谈一个解决方案之前
So before I talk to you about a solution,
让我们看看 TypeScript 和 Flow 可以为我们做什么。
let's look at what TypeScript and
Flow can do for us.
从广义上说，他们的好处是什么 ?
What are their benefits, broadly speaking?
我知道这很有道理
I understand that this is a very
sort of reduced argument,
有一个更复杂和生动的生态系统
there is a much more complex and
vivid ecosystem.
我并不是说任何关于这些事的说法都是关于
And I don't mean in any way to talk down
about these, there's a whole course on
Fron趋向 Masters，甚至可能不止一个，关于 TypeScript。
Frontend Masters, or maybe even
more than one, about TypeScript.
这些都是很棒的工具，他们背后有智慧的人。
These are great tools with fantastic,
intelligent people behind them.
但从广义上来说，它们在生态系统中是合适的地方吗 ?
But just sort of broadly speaking,
where do they fit within the ecosystem?
他们会为我们做些什么
What are they gonna do for us?
第一，他们会发现与类型相关的错误，
Well, number one,
they're gonna catch type-related mistakes,
那是件好事
that's a good thing.
我们需要帮助捕捉与类型相关的错误。
We need help catching our
type-related mistakes.
我想有个能理解我想做什么的工具
I would like to have a tool that
understood what I wanna do with types, and
当我没做正确的时候就帮了我
helped me figure out when I
didn't do that correctly.
这会让我更有编码器
That would make me a better coder.
第二，因为输入在代码中，所以它们会传达类型意图。
Number two, they do communicate type
intent, because the typing is in the code.
当然，他们只有在作出推断时才有模式。
Course they have modes where
they are doing only inference.
但本质上， TypeScript 的大卖点和
But essentially,
the big selling point of TypeScript and
流是您可以直接在代码顶部对这些类型的注释进行分层。
Flow is that you can layer these type
annotations directly on top of the code.
在某些方面，你这么做的最大原因之一是
And in some respects, one of the biggest
reasons why you do that is because
这会让你的密码更加明显
it's gonna make your code more obvious.
那么我可以清楚地看到这个东西是一个整数，
Well, I can clearly see that
that thing is an integer,
或者那东西是绳子对吧
or that thing is a string, right?
那就好
That's good.
第三，我认为这常常被忽视，但是
Number three, and
I think this is often overlooked, but
也许是最大的原因之一
maybe one of the biggest things.
是这样做的吗
Is that by doing so,
选择进入这个系统你会得到惊人的数量
by choosing to opt into that system,
you get an amazing amount
通过工具生态系统的反馈，可以直接显示在您的标识中。
of feedback through the tooling ecosystem
that can show up live directly in your ID.
太棒了我见过一些自动完成的
It's awesome,
I've seen some of the auto completing and
有关 " 类型脚本 " 之类的内容的飞行推论和类型分析。
on the fly inferences and type analysis
that something like TypeScript does.
TypeScript 在这一点上比流好很多，但是
TypeScript does it a lot better
than Flow at this point, but
我确定 Flow 会迎头赶上的对吧
I'm sure Flow will catch up, right?
我认为 IDE 与 TypeScript 集成
I think IDE integration with TypeScript
比我在 IDE 中被集成的任何项目都要好
is better than any project that I've ever
seen integrated in an IDE, it's fantastic.
我正好没使用 IDE
I happened to not use IDEs.
所以我不是从这件事中获益的
So I happened to not benefit
from any of that, but
这并不意味着我不尊重它我觉得这很棒
that doesn't mean I don't respect it,
I think it's fantastic.
>> 演讲者 1: 这些工具有一些警告。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: There are some
caveats to these tools.
第一，你依赖的，你所依赖的
Number one, the inferencing
that you rely upon, which you
只要你有一个你不会讨厌的地方
rely upon inferencing whenever you have
a place where you're not gonna annotate.
[ LAUGH] 你真正依赖的推断只是一个最好的猜测。
[LAUGH] The inferencing that you
rely on really is just a best guess.
这不是实心的
It's not rock solid.
我们能在编译时尽可能地猜测一些事情。
We're guessing something as
much as we can at compile time.
我们不知道在运行时到底会发生什么
We don't really know what's
actually gonna happen at run time.
因为注释是可选的，所以实际上是第二个。
That flows from number two actually,
because the annotations are optional.
这意味着您所在团队的开发者如果未对其进行注释
Which means the developers on your team,
if they don't put an annotation on
变量， TypeScript 将缺省为任何类型，除非您已关闭。
a variable, TypeScript will default to the
any type unless you have that turned off.
它将缺省为任何类型，然后您将无法从中获益。
It will default to the any type and then
you're not getting any benefit out of it.
所以它是一个选入系统。
So it is an opt-in system.
如果你不选择在某个特定的地方，你只能得到最好的猜测。
And if you don't opt in in a particular
place you're only getting a best guess.
如果你是个非法的人
It can lead to a false
sense of security if you're
不是很小心你的用法
not being very careful
about your usage of it.
>> 演讲者 1: 这是我一直在说的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: This flows from really
what I've been saying the whole time.
那个没有打字的地方在你的代码里
That any place that isn't typed,
either in your code or
您的代码所涉及的内容不在您的应用程序中。
things that your code touches
that are not in your application.
如果没有输入，则存在不确定性。
If they aren't typed there is uncertainty.